qatcom.com 2011-05-29

# Privacy

_**Privacy Policy Statement**_

This is the privacy policy for all web sites operated by Qatcom LLC and administrator of this site.

Contact Information:

Qatcom LLC  
PO Box 24863  
Ground Floor  
Al Mirqab Tower   
Doha   
Qatar

Tel: +974 4217140 Fax: +974 4217141

Email: _[admin@qatcom.com](mailto:admin@qatcom.com)_ _[www.qatcom.com](http://www.qatcom.com/)_

Since its inception, Qatcom LLC has developed relationships with our customers and users based on respect and integrity. We are aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit our website and provide us with information and are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors whilst providing the highest possible quality of service. The Privacy Notice below is posted to demonstrate our adherence to the practices you'll find common to the best websites online. We promise that we will treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history. 

Your personal details are not held or used without your permission.

By visiting our website you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

_YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION_

You acknowledge and agree that we may collect information about you. The information may be obtained from;

  * Personal information provided voluntarily 

  * From publicly available sources of information

  * Website usage information through tracking your click behaviour 

  * Aggregated data, measuring traffic to Qatcom, but not relating to you personally 

You may decide whether to provide any information we seek from you. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide all services to you.

_DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA_.

Personal data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of Qatcom, or in connection with the business of Qatcom for further processing in accordance with the purposes to which you have subsequently consented. 

Qatcom may also share information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interest, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this website, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event. 

_DATA INTEGRITY AND SECURITY_

We keep your personal data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.

In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology, such as industry standard firewalls and password protection.

Our employees who have access to personal data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols and strict standards of confidentiality. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

_COOKIES_

Like most sites, for account management purposes, Qatcom uses cookies. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. Cookies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns to better understand our user base and to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. 

_LINKS TO OTHER SITES_

The Qatcom website contains links to other sites. Those sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites since we do not control them.

_THIRD PARTY SITES_

You may click-through to third party sites from our sites in which case we recommend that you refer to the privacy statement of the sites you visit. Qatcomâ€™s collection statement and privacy policy apply to Qatcomâ€™s website only and Qatcom assumes no responsibility for information and content of third party sites. 

_BUSINESS TRANSFERS_

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Qatcom, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, a user's personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.  

_CONSENT AND CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY_

By using our site or services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement. Qatcom may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. If and when we do, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**_HELP US TO ENSURE WE HOLD ACCURATE INFORMATION_**

Qatcom takes all reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent on the information you provide. That's why we recommend that you:

  * let us know if there are any errors in your personal information; and 

  * keep us up to date with changes to personal information such as your name or address. by contacting us: _[http://www.qatcom.com/contact-qatcom](http://www.qatcom.com/contact-qatcom)_

_CONTACT US_

Please feel free to contact us at any time with any questions you may have regarding our privacy statement. _[http://www.qatcom.com/contact-qatcom](http://www.qatcom.com/contact-qatcom)_
